

Nayeli A. Pérez T.

nayeliperez.com

nayeliaperezt@gmail.com (915) 449 • 3373

San Antonio, TX

ín /nayelipín nayeliprz11

Hello! My name is Nayeli Pérez; nice to meet you. I am a multidisciplinary designer with a keen interest in user interface design, front-end development, and the overall challenge of designing digital experiences in an increasingly digital world. I also particularly enjoy the challenges of branding/identity design and design systems.

EDUCATION

AUG 2012 - MAY 2016 Bachelors of Arts in Communication, CUM LAUDE

Minor in Studio Art & Art History -

Photography Concentration

Trinity University - San Antonio, TX

FALL 2015 Study Abroad

Studio Art Centers International (SACI) - Florence, Italy

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

AUG 2013 - DEC 2015 Photographer

Trinity University Campus Publications - San Antonio, TX

JAN 2015 - MAY 2016 Graphic Design Intern

Trinity University Press - San Antonio, TX

JAN 2016 - MAY 2016 Art Director

Trinity University's Skyline 2016 Magazine - San Antonio, TX

AUG 2016 - AUG 2018 Lead Graphic Designer

esd & associates Digital Marketing - San Antonio, TX

SEP 2018 - PRESENT UI/UX Designer

Chargify - San Antonio, TX

LANGUAGES

Spanish & English
Native Speaker

SKILLS

InDesign

Photoshop

Illustrator

Lightroom

Sketch

Figma

Invision

HTML/CSS/SCSS

Wordpress

Webflow

Bootstrap

Extensive Photography and Darkroom Printing experience